planetdiscover.com 2013-05-30

# Mobile Apps, Local Search, Business Directory, Events, Ad System – Planet Discover

Last Updated: January 4, 2011

We take seriously your interest in how your information is collected and used. Please read the following to learn about our Privacy Notice.

This Privacy Notice discloses the privacy practices of this website (the "Site"). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using the Site, and the ways in which we use and share this information. This Privacy Notice does not apply to any information you may provide to us, or that we may collect, offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail).

Please read this Privacy Notice carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site, and any dispute over our online privacy practices, is governed by this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Service. Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Notice at some point in the future, in which case we'll post the revised Privacy Notice on this website and update the "Last Updated" date to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Notice as modified.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:

Mark Faris  
Online Privacy Coordinator  
Gannett Law Department  
7950 Jones Branch Drive  
McLean, VA 22107

## How We Collect and Use Information

We may collect and store information, including personally identifiable information (such as your name, postal address or email address) or other information, that you voluntarily supply to us while on our Site. Some examples of this type of information include information that you electronically submit when you contact us with a request for information.

We also collect, through a variety of technologies and practices, and store non-personally identifiable information that is generated automatically as you navigate through the Site. For example, we may collect information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on the Site. We also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a "cookie" to enhance your experience with the Site. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us deliver advertisements, identify how many unique users visit us, and track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the Site where you may have entered preference information before. This Site also may use web beacons (single-pixel graphic files also known as "transparent GIFs") to access cookies and to count users who visit the Site or open HTML-formatted email messages.

If you want to limit the non-personally identifiable information that is automatically collected while you use our Site, most Web browsers allow you to disable certain functionality or set certain privacy settings. For example, to disable cookies using Internet Explorer, select "Internet Options" under the Tools menu and click on "Privacy." Select "High" or "Block All Cookies." To disable cookies using Mozilla Firefox, select "Options" under the "Tools" menu. If you choose to disable cookies or turn off other functionality, you may not be able to use or participate in some or all of the features offered through the Site.

The information we collect may be collected directly by us, or it may be collected by a third-party website hosting provider, or another third-party service provider, on our behalf.

We use the information we collect from you while you are using the Site in a variety of ways, including, for example, to process your registration request, provide you with services and communications that you have requested, send you email updates and other communications, customize features and advertising that appear on the Site, deliver our Site content to you, measure Site traffic, measure user interests and traffic patterns, and improve the Site and the services and features offered via the Site.

In addition, we may use any information submitted by or collected from you via the Site for any purpose related to the Site, including to contact you for customer service purposes, to inform you of important changes or additions to our Site or the services offered over our Site, and to send you administrative notices and any other communications that we believe may be of interest to you.

We also may provide your information to our affiliates or to third parties, including our third party service providers and contractors, for purposes related to Site administration and other services.

If you do not wish your personally identifiable information to be used or shared for these purposes, send a letter to the Online Privacy Coordinator whose contact information is listed at the end of this Privacy Notice.

Please be aware that we may occasionally release information about our visitors if required to do so by law or if, in our business judgment, such disclosure is reasonably necessary: (a) to comply with legal process; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service; or (c) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of our Site, us, our affiliates, our officers, directors, employees, representatives, our licensors, other users, and/or the public.

Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we sell some or all of our assets, or our Site is acquired by another company, information about our Site users may be among the transferred assets.

## Children's Privacy Statement

This children's privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of 13, and provides important information regarding their rights under federal law with respect to such information.

  * This Site is not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 as part of the Site. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of 13 from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of 13 as part of the Site, we will delete such information from our records.
  * Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 via the Site, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
  * We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Site.
  * Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 via the Site, we do NOT condition the participation of a child under 13 in the Site's online activities on providing personally identifiable information.

## How To Make Changes to Your Information

If you have any questions about modifying your preference information, please contact us.

## Storage of Information

All information we gather on our Site is stored within a database to which only we and our hosting services provider are provided access. However, as effective as the reasonable security measures implemented by us may be, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our Siteâ€™s servers or databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

## Questions Regarding Privacy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, our privacy practices, or your dealings with us, you can contact:

Mark Faris  
Online Privacy Coordinator  
Gannett Law Department  
7950 Jones Branch Drive  
McLean, VA 22107
